[{"answer": "Well, the Muslim Brotherhood is known for its solid coordination.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "How dangerous could it be, do you think?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "I'm doing well.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Mr. Speaker, how are you?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "This is all a bit of fast, isn't it?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "You know, the practical reality is that the American military is very often a stabilizing and in the long-run modernizing force and they're having a relationship between the American military and local militaries is often very good.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Because what happens if other countries now, emboldened by what they've seen in Egypt, emboldened by President Obama's reaction, if their military rise up and take control, and say well, hang on, it's not a coup, it's exactly the same as what's happening in Egypt?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "I think the proper course of action is to be very, very steady.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "What is the proper course of action now, do you think, for President Obama to take?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "I don't think we're right back where we were, Piers, because in 2011, two and a half years ago there was the excitement and the enthusiasm about -- and hope for a democratic process, and that has been killed now, and we have hundreds and hundreds of dead people and their blood on top of that.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "And what has happened to the idealistic dream of the Arab spring?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, most of the studies have been done at the National Institute of Health do indicate that there are impacts on people's brains that are real.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "At what point, if it seems to be just basically something that could help people who are sick, or can be used recreationally like alcohol and tobacco, why bother being so anti of it being legalized?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "This is such stupid childish overreaction that I'm astonished.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Well, what is your view of that?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "I think it's all a bit ridiculous.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Well, let me, first of all, say about stop-and-frisk that every time I get on an airplane I'm stopped and frisked, and I accept that as a part of travel in America, and every person who travels is stopped and frisked, and it happens to all of us.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "The question then becomes, is that acceptable if a certain element of society, from a certain race, are committing a certain type of crime?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, how about --", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "How would you feel -- how would you feel if 85, 90 percent of all those who are frisked at airports were black or Latinos?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, here's --", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "But of course there isn't really, is there?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Well, it is.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "That's a pretty expensive experiment in terms of lives of young black men who will be killed?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "What's been going on here actually all day, Piers, has been a fundraiser for Hannah Anderson and her family.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Casey, what was happening there tonight and how would you describe Hannah Anderson's demeanor?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Well, they're not saying what they intend to do with it.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Casey, just -- just quickly, what does the family intend to do with the money that's being raised here?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "I'm not surprised at all.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "But what do you think?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Absolutely, Piers.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "It sort of creates a -- a potential picture that maybe at the start of this, she thought she was going on some new adventure, oblivious to the mayhem he had caused without her knowing about her mother and her son being killed -- and her brother being killed?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "But it certainly, it answers some of the questions about why perhaps when they met complete strangers on horseback, she didn't immediately raise a red flag?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "O: I think there's a big part of families who have been traumatized to try to normalize everything and try to bring everything back to a stable point.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "But what other things should she be doing, do you think?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Yes, this was the most emotional part of the day.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "But also very fascinating about Paris Jackson, Michael's daughter and the trauma, in particularly, that she has suffered?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "You've got the look, the face, the -- the -- you probably sing as well, right?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "You know, it's rough.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "How would you describe the reality of what her life has been like?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Well, he taught them to always listen and to watch everything that's around them and to pay attention, you know.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "What kind of things?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "It's hard for my grandmother.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "How is Kathryn dealing with this trial because it must be a big ordeal for her to so many painful details and revelations about Michael being regurgitated?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "By (ph) questions -- you know, I don't know, to me, it's normal.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "How would you describe being a Jackson?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Have justice.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "What would the Jackson family -- what would Paris and Michael's other children -- what does everybody want to happen here?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "For the truth to come out and it is coming out.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "And then what would you see justice as being?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "I don't even want to get there.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "What do you believe the truth is?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Yes, all of us.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "That's what the family thinks?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Do you think the trial is going the right way?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "You know, I met her once.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Do you know Debbie?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Is she engaged in at all?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "She's trying to avoid it?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "It does, Piers.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "But actually, it does have really damaging effects, doesn't have, on the victims to have to put up with this kind of harassment?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Well, I'm a very good woman to where I can forgive somebody that has done wrong to me.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Peggy Shannon, when you hear him being apparently so contrite, do you forgive him or -- or not?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Well, people are surprised that, as a great grandmother, that this happened to me.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Did you hear other stories?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Peggy Shannon and Gloria Allred, thank you, both, very much for indeed for coming on.", "docId": "130815pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "And we're looking forward to the outcome of that investigation and the decision by the attorney general of California as to whether or not they want to proceed with criminal charges or not and if so, for whom?", "qSentId": 547}]